Ever had the feeling that this thing is
spying on you? Well, you would be
correct. It is listening to you all the
time. And I for one would like to stop
the spy. With everything going on in my
life from old Bibles and solar science
to free energy, I'm switching to a new
phone. This is the Alcatel WP500 Ultra.
The difference is obvious. Look at the
size. Look how big they are. See that
little button right there? Watch what
happens. Flip.
Recording, camera, location disabled. As
soon as you hit that switch, the camera,
the microphone, and the GPS have no
power going to them. Built in the
hardware. One-click privacy protection.
This comes with 16 GB built in that's
connected to a cloud that's monitored by
some tech giant somewhere. This comes
with 1 TB built in that can expand to 2
TB and no need to connect to cloud with
that kind of storage. Basically, little
computer. [music] Battery's pretty nuts,
too. This is 3,500 mA. This is 20,000
mA. 7x. And it's a portable power pack,
too. The power port is power in or power
out. You can charge your other devices
off of this thing. This might be my
favorite thing, the thermal imaging
camera. See those running devices over
there? Look, they're warm. You can look
for faulty electrical wiring, knowing
what circuits are energized. Fridge is
wild. You can see your reflection on it.
You can see the heat coming off the
side.
>> [music]
>> And then when you open it up,
look how cold it is in there. They told
me it's drop-proof [clears throat] up to
one height.
It's got a built-in case and a screen
protector. And it evidently works. They
also told me it's waterproof.
Um
How to testing done right. It is
definitely waterproof.
Look at shaking water out of this guy.
It's got a real-life flashlight. Let me
show you the difference. This is an
iPhone light.
This is an Alcatel light. You can tell
the difference. Look at that. Alcatel
iPhone
I mean, come on, bro. And unlike a
normal phone, this Alcatel has night
vision. You can see who'll be creeping
in the night. Bro, I'm blown away. If
you're a contractor, it has a plumb bob.
Is my light level?
Yes, it is. And the picture hanger.
>> [music]
>> Bro, that looks perfect. I ain't going
to lie, I love this phone so much, I'm
just going to throw it. It's unbeatable,
unbreakable, and I am determined to stop
the spy. I am done with the
disposaphone, I am going to the robot
phone. This Alpha Stel WP500 is too
legit to quit.